A Guide to the Robert Young Clay Papers, 1789-2010 (bulk 1920-2007)
Library of Virginia
- Series II. Subject Files, 1789-2010., Extent: 41 boxes. (Box 98-138)
  - Genealogical Research - Platting. (Box 110, Folder 10)
  - Genealogical Research - Social Security Records. (Box 110, Folder 11)
  - Genealogical Research - Sources, How-To, Forms, etc.. (Box 110, Folder 12-14)
  - Genealogical Research - Spanish-American War Records. (Box 110, Folder 15)
  - Genealogical Research - Switzerland. (Box 110, Folder 16)
  - Genealogical Research - Tax Records. (Box 110, Folder 17)
  - Genealogical Societies - Virginia. (Box 110, Folder 18)
  - Genealogy, Cal's Columns, and Notes. (Box 110, Folder 19)
  - Genealogy - Class Notes. (Box 110, Folder 20)
  - General Court. (Box 110, Folder 21)
  - Gentry, Daphne. (Box 110, Folder 22)
  - Georgia Sources. (Box 110, Folder 23)
  - Germany. (Box 110, Folder 24)
  - Get Well Cards/Notes, 2005. (Box 111, Folder 1)
  - Gilmore. (Box 111, Folder 2)
  - Godwin, Governor Mills E. Jr.. (Box 111, Folder 3)
  - Goodies. (Box 111, Folder 4-6)
  - Grady, Pattie. (Box 111, Folder 7)
  - Greathouse, Nancy. (Box 111, Folder 8)
  - Green. (Box 111, Folder 9)
  - Green, Hallie. (Box 111, Folder 10-11)
  - Gregory, Eve. (Box 111, Folder 12)
  - Gregory, Sue Ann. (Box 111, Folder 13)
  - Griffey, Irene. (Box 111, Folder 14)
  - GRIVA - Raleigh Trip, 2002. (Box 111, Folder 15)
  - Grundset, Eric. (Box 111, Folder 16)
  - Guerra, Armando. (Box 111, Folder 17)
  - Guide to Pre-1904 Municipal Records in Archives, VSLA. (Box 111, Folder 18)
  - Gwaltney. (Box 112, Folder 1-2)
  - Gwaltney-Amos. (Box 112, Folder 3)
  - Gwaltney Family Papers, 1924-1990. (Box 112, Folder 4-5)
  - Gwaltney, Helen Davis - Family Bible. (Box 164)
  - Gwaltney, Mildred. (Box 112, Folder 6)
  - Gwaltney, Milton - Articles. (Box 112, Folder 7)
  - Gwaltney - Welsh History. (Box 112, Folder 8)
  - The Amazing Story of the Gwaltneys in America by Sharon Taylor, 1982. (Box 112, Folder 9)
  - Hale, Jo Yancey. (Box 113, Folder 1)
  - Hamlin, Madge. (Box 113, Folder 2)
  - Handley, Bessie Clay. (Box 113, Folder 3)
  - Handley, Helen. (Box 113, Folder 4)
  - Handwriting. (Box 113, Folder 5)
  - Harmon, Joann Paschall. (Box 113, Folder 6)
  - Harper, Mary Hunter. (Box 113, Folder 7)
  - Harper - Smith County, TN (Van A. Stilley). (Box 113, Folder 8)
  - Haun, Wynette. (Box 113, Folder 9)
  - Heagerty, Gregory H.. (Box 113, Folder 10)
  - Heiss, Willard. (Box 113, Folder 11)
  - Hemphill, John. (Box 113, Folder 12)
  - Henderson, Dr. W.R.. (Box 113, Folder 13)
  - Heraldry Society. (Box 113, Folder 14)
  - Hersch, Jane Buckles. (Box 113, Folder 15)
  - Hicks. (Box 113, Folder 16)
  - History of Smith County by Dr. J.W. Bowen. (Box 113, Folder 17)
  - Hoar, Jay S.. (Box 113, Folder 18)
  - Honts, Emily. (Box 113, Folder 19)
  - Hopkins-Logwood. (Box 113, Folder 20)
  - House Research. (Box 113, Folder 21)
  - Howard Female College (Gallatin, TN) - Catalogue, 1892-1893. (Box 113, Folder 22)
  - Howe, Mary Ellen (Bailey Family). (Box 113, Folder 23)
  - Hudspeth, Ruth. (Box 113, Folder 24)
  - Hudson, Frank Parker. (Box 113, Folder 25)
  - Huguenots. (Box 113, Folder 26)
  - Hutcheson, Glenda. (Box 113, Folder 27)
  - Hutchinson, R.M.. (Box 114, Folder 1)
  - Illinois. (Box 114, Folder 2)
  - Indentured Servants. (Box 114, Folder 3)
  - Indiana. (Box 114, Folder 4)
  - Inheritance. (Box 114, Folder 5)
  - Interlibrary Loan - Newspapers. (Box 114, Folder 6)
  - Ireland. (Box 114, Folder 7)
  - Ironside, Xavier. (Box 114, Folder 8)
  - Jeffries, James. (Box 114, Folder 9)
  - Jennings, Dr. Thomas H.. (Box 114, Folder 10)
  - Job Descriptions. (Box 114, Folder 11)
  - Johns, Jean. (Box 114, Folder 12)
  - Johnson, Lois. (Box 114, Folder 13)
  - Jones, Agnes C.. (Box 114, Folder 14)
  - Jones, Louise. (Box 114, Folder 15)
  - Jones, Robert A.W.. (Box 114, Folder 16)
  - Jones, Col. Robert. (Box 114, Folder 17)
  - Jones, Ruth Jane Clay. (Box 114, Folder 18)
  - Jones, Sally and Jackson. (Box 114, Folder 19)
  - Jordan, W.T.. (Box 114, Folder 20)
  - Joyner, Peggy Shomo. (Box 114, Folder 21)
  - Keen, Jim. (Box 114, Folder 22)
  - Kegley, Mary B.. (Box 114, Folder 23)
  - Kemper, Janette. (Box 114, Folder 24)
  - Kentucky. (Box 114, Folder 25)
  - Kilby, Craig. (Box 114, Folder 26)
  - Killian, Mrs. Harvey. (Box 114, Folder 27)
  - King, George H.S.. (Box 114, Folder 28)
  - King, Helen. (Box 114, Folder 29)
  - Knighton, Charles von Dietrich. (Box 114, Folder 30)
  - Knoxville, TN. (Box 114, Folder 31)
  - Langston, Diane. (Box 114, Folder 32)
  - Latin Numerals. (Box 114, Folder 33)
  - Ledger - William S. Alexander (Dixon Springs, TN), 1841-1845, 1868-1872. (Box 167)
  - Legal Terms. (Box 114, Folder 34)
  - Legislature. (Box 114, Folder 35)
  - Letters (NRN), 1988-1990. (Box 114, Folder 36)
  - Library Forms. (Box 114, Folder 37)
  - Library of Virginia. (Box 115, Folder 1-5)
  - Library of Virginia - Guide to Resources. (Box 115, Folder 6-7)
  - Library Procedures. (Box 116, Folder 1)
  - Library Staff Memos, 1977-1978. (Box 116, Folder 2)
  - Linn, Jo White. (Box 116, Folder 3)
  - Litchfield, Rita. (Box 116, Folder 4)
  - Little, Barbara Vines. (Box 116, Folder 5)
  - Logan-Terry. (Box 116, Folder 6)
  - Lonas, Jo. (Box 116, Folder 7)
  - Loomis. (Box 116, Folder 8)
  - Lowem Joan Clay. (Box 116, Folder 9)
  - Lowry, Houston. (Box 116, Folder 10)
  - Lowry, Joe. (Box 116, Folder 11-14)
  - Luther, Carol J. (Joe B. Lowry). (Box 116, Folder 15)
  - Lynch - Dixon Springs, TN. (Box 116, Folder 16)
  - MacDonald, Edgar. (Box 117, Folder 17)
  - Maggart, Sue W.. (Box 116, Folder 18)
  - Mahoney, Bessie Day Gann. (Box 116, Folder 19-20)
  - Manahan, Jack. (Box 116, Folder 21)
  - Maps. (Box 117, Folder 1-2)
  - Maps of Tennessee and Other Southern States for Genealogical Searching - Compiled by Pollyanna Creekmore (Map-case 56, Drawer 5)
  - Martin-Logwood. (Box 117, Folder 3)
  - Martin, Louise Gray. (Box 117, Folder 4)
  - Maryland Families. (Box 117, Folder 5)
  - Maryland Families and Research. (Box 117, Folder 6)
  - Maryland Hall of Records. (Box 117, Folder 7)
  - Maryland Records. (Box 117, Folder 8)
  - Maxey. (Box 117, Folder 9)
  - Maxey, Charles. (Box 117, Folder 10)
  - Maxey, Edward. (Box 117, Folder 11)
  - Maxwell, Littleton. (Box 117, Folder 12)
  - McCartey, William. (Box 117, Folder 13)
  - McCay, Betty. (Box 117, Folder 14)
  - McConnaughey, Gibson J.. (Box 117, Folder 15)
  - McGuire, Elaine Young. (Box 117, Folder 16)
  - McKee, Marianne. (Box 117, Folder 17)
  - Meador, Mary M.. (Box 117, Folder 18)
  - Meigs, James. (Box 117, Folder 19)
  - Meinhardt, Maura. (Box 117, Folder 20)
  - Membership Papers. (Box 117, Folder 21-22)
  - Memorandum Book, 1978-1979. (Box 117, Folder 23)
  - Memorial Foundation of the Germanna Colonies. (Box 118, Folder 1)
  - Middle Tennessee Genealogical Society. (Box 118, Folder 2)
  - The Midlander - Middle Tennessee State Teachers College, 1933. (Box 118, Folder 3)
  - Military Records. (Box 118, Folder 4)
  - William Stuart Miller Family History by William F. Bewell. (Box 118, Folder 5)
  - Mills, Elizabeth Shown. (Box 118, Folder 6)
  - Mills, Jesse C.. (Box 118, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous. (Box 118, Folder 8)
  - Missouri. (Box 118, Folder 9)
  - Mitchell, Georgia Duke. (Box 118, Folder 10)
  - Moistner, Jeanne. (Box 118, Folder 11)
  - Monteiro, Rose Marie. (Box 118, Folder 12)
  - Moomaw. (Box 118, Folder 13)
  - Moore, Joanne Cullom. (Box 118, Folder 14)
  - Moore, Mae D.. (Box 118, Folder 15)
  - Moore, Roberta Gann. (Box 118, Folder 16)
  - Morgan, Don. (Box 118, Folder 17)
  - Morton, Belle Clay Lyons. (Box 118, Folder 18)
  - Mountcastle, Dick. (Box 118, Folder 19)
  - Mutual Assurance Society Policy Index. (Box 118, Folder 20)
  - Names. (Box 118, Folder 21)
  - Nance, Joanne L.. (Box 118, Folder 22)
  - Nansemond Marriages, 1811. (Box 118, Folder 23)
  - Nashville Research. (Box 118, Folder 24)
  - Neville, John. (Box 118, Folder 25)
  - New York. (Box 118, Folder 26)
  - New York Public Library. (Box 118, Folder 27)
  - Newman Library. (Box 118, Folder 28)
  - Newsletters - Chesterfield County Historical Society, 1995-1996. (Box 119, Folder 1)
  - Newsletters - Dinwiddie County Historical Society, 2003. (Box 119, Folder 2)
  - Newsletters - Friends of the Virginia State Archives, 2004, 2006. (Box 119, Folder 3)
  - Newsletters - The Gann Gazette, 2001-2007. (Box 119, Folder 4-6)
  - Newsletters - Genealogical Society of the Northern Neck of Virginia, 2001. (Box 119, Folder 7)
  - Newsletters - Gore Family Newsletter, 1997. (Box 119, Folder 8)
  - Newsletters - GRIVA News and Notes, 2001-2005. (Box 119, Folder 9-10)
  - Newsletters - Klee Kronicles, 1994-1996. (Box 119, Folder 11)
  - Newsletters - Middle Tennessee Genealogical Society, 2000, 2005. (Box 120, Folder 1)
  - Newsletters - North Carolina Genealogical Society, 1982. (Box 120, Folder 2)
  - Newsletters - Smith County Historical and Genealogical Society, 1996, 2005. (Box 120, Folder 3)
  - Newsletters - Tidewater Virginia Families: A Magazine of History and Genealogy, 1992-1999. (Box 120)
  - Newsletters - Virginia Genealogical Society Newsletter, 1983, 2003-2010. (Box 121)
  - Newsletters - The Virginia Genealogist, 1993, 2001. (Box 121)
  - Newspapers (Partial and Complete Issues). (Box 171)
  - Norris, June Capps. (Box 122, Folder 1)
  - North Carolina. (Box 122, Folder 2)
  - North Carolina Counties. (Box 122, Folder 3)
  - North Carolina Local Records Arrangement. (Box 122, Folder 4)
  - North Carolina - Published County Records. (Box 122, Folder 5)
  - North Carolina Sources. (Box 122, Folder 6)
  - North Carolina State Archives Guide to County Records. (Box 122, Folder 7)
  - Northampton/Accomack - 1704 Quit Rent Rolls. (Box 122, Folder 8)
  - Numbering Systems. (Box 122, Folder 9)
  - Obituaries (A-Z) Group I. (Box 122, Folder 10-14)
  - Obituaries (A-Z) Group I. (Box 123, Folder 1-4)
  - Obituaries (A-Z) Group II. (Box 123, Folder 5-9)
  - Obituaries (A-Z) Group II. (Box 124, Folder 1-2)
  - Obituaries (Non-Family). (Box 124, Folder 3)
  - Ohio. (Box 124, Folder 4)
  - Ohio Land Records. (Box 124, Folder 5)
  - Oklahoma. (Box 124, Folder 6)
  - Orchards. (Box 124, Folder 7)
  - Order of First Families of North Carolina. (Box 124, Folder 8-11)
  - Order of First Families of Virginia. (Box 124, Folder 12-16)
  - Order of First Families of Virginia. (Box 125, Folder 1-3)
  - Order of First Families of Virginia, 1994-1996. (Box 125, Folder 4-6)
  - Order of First Families of Virginia - Records at LVA. (Box 125, Folder 7)
  - Order of the Crown in America. (Box 125, Folder 8)
  - Oregon. (Box 125, Folder 9)
  - Organ, Fred Marshall. (Box 125, Folder 10)
  - Organ, George Benjamin. (Box 125, Folder 11)
  - Organ, Robert L.. (Box 125, Folder 12)
  - Osbornes (Chesterfield County, VA). (Box 125, Folder 13)
  - Overhultz, Georgia. (Box 125, Folder 14)
  - Overman, Lou. (Box 125, Folder 15)
  - Owen, James Welch. (Box 125, Folder 16)
  - Page, William D.. (Box 126, Folder 1)
  - Palatines to America. (Box 126, Folder 2)
  - Parker, Annie. (Box 126, Folder 3)
  - Parker Family Records (Margaret J. Beeks). (Box 126, Folder 4)
  - Parker, Paulette Keith. (Box 126, Folder 5)
  - Parkhurst, Paul Wilson. (Box 126, Folder 6)
  - Parrish, Barbara J.. (Box 126, Folder 7)
  - Partlow, Thomas E.. (Box 126, Folder 8)
  - Paschall, Margaret. (Box 126, Folder 9)
  - Passenger Lists - National Archives. (Box 126, Folder 10)
  - Patillo, Dorothy Erman. (Box 126, Folder 11)
  - Peacock, Peggy. (Box 126, Folder 12-13)
  - Peak, Paul R.. (Box 126, Folder 14)
  - Pearce, Bertha Clay. (Box 126, Folder 15)
  - Pennsylvania. (Box 126, Folder 16)
  - Platting Land. (Box 126, Folder 17)
  - Pointer. (Box 126, Folder 18)
  - Poorwhite. (Box 126, Folder 19)
  - Price, Prentiss. (Box 126, Folder 20)
  - Price, Prentiss - Notes. (Box 126, Folder 21)
  - Prince George County Wills and Marriages, Pre-1865. (Box 126, Folder 22)
  - Public Records Office. (Box 126, Folder 23)
  - Pugh, Howard. (Box 126, Folder 24)
  - Pygott. (Box 126, Folder 25-26)
  - Quintrell, Earl W.. (Box 126, Folder 27)
  - Radford. (Box 127, Folder 1-2)
  - Radford - Essex County, VA. (Box 127, Folder 3)
  - Radford-Hicks. (Box 127, Folder 4)
  - Radford/Hicks/Maxey - Cumberland County, KY (Ross Chappell). (Box 127, Folder 5)
  - Radford, John. (Box 127, Folder 6)
  - Radford, Reuben Davis. (Box 127, Folder 7)
  - Radford, Stephen and Vanessa. (Box 127, Folder 8)
  - Radford, William Layton. (Box 127, Folder 9)
  - Ancestors of Stephen Walker Radford. (Box 127, Folder 10-12)
  - Ancestors of Stephen Walker Radford. (Box 128, Folder 1)
  - Stephen Walker Radford - Charts. (Box 128, Folder 2)
  - Ramey. (Box 128, Folder 3)
  - Randolph County (IN) Genealogical Society. (Box 128, Folder 4)
  - Ratledge, Anne. (Box 128, Folder 5)
  - Raye, Larry. (Box 128, Folder 6-9)
  - Raye, Sally Cox. (Box 128, Folder 10)
  - Read, Agatha B. (Nashville Landlady). (Box 128, Folder 11)
  - Reagan, Ronald - Genealogy. (Box 128, Folder 12)
  - Regnal Years. (Box 128, Folder 13)
  - Recipes. (Box 128, Folder 14-16)
  - Relationship Charts. (Box 128, Folder 17)
  - Reinowski, Priscilla R.. (Box 128, Folder 18)
  - Replacements, Ltd.. (Box 128, Folder 19)
  - Report Cards. (Box 128, Folder 20)
  - Research After 1920. (Box 129, Folder 1)
  - Research in Mid-Atlantic States: A Bibliographic Essay. (Box 129, Folder 2)
  - Research Notes (Abstracts, Transcriptions, etc.). (Box 129, Folder 3-8)
  - Research Trip to Public Record Office, 1982. (Box 129, Folder 9-10)
  - Revolutionary War Records - National Archives. (Box 129, Folder 11)
  - Revolutionary War Records - Pay Rolls (Auditor's Office) (Map-case 56, Drawer 5)
  - Richmond City Banner. (Box 129, Folder 12)
  - Ricks, Donald M.. (Box 129, Folder 13)
  - Riffe, Andrew. (Box 129, Folder 14)
  - Roanoke Public Library. (Box 129, Folder 15)
  - "Roots" TV Program. (Box 129, Folder 16)
  - Roper, Kate. (Box 129, Folder 17)
  - Rosebloom, Margaret. (Box 129, Folder 18)
  - Ross, Evelyn. (Box 130, Folder 1-7)
  - Ross, Joel. (Box 130, Folder 8)
  - Salmon, John and Emily. (Box 130, Folder 9)
  - Sammis, Lucetta. (Box 130, Folder 10)
  - Sanders-Alexander Family Bible Records. (Box 130, Folder 11)
  - Scherr, Arthur. (Box 130, Folder 12)
  - School Account Book, 1957. (Box 130, Folder 13)
  - Scrapbook - Ruth Ballou Clay - Brandon Training School, 1916-1918. (Box 163)
  - Scrapbook, Helen Davis, 1931-1938. (Box 165)
  - Scrapbooks. (Box 165-166)
  - Shack, Imogene Young. (Box 130, Folder 14)
  - Scott, Betty M.. (Box 130, Folder 15)
  - Shaver, Addie. (Box 130, Folder 16)
  - Shepard, E. Lee. (Box 130, Folder 17)
  - Shook, Pat Fox. (Box 130, Folder 18)
  - Shouse, Walter. (Box 130, Folder 19)
  - Showaker, Clara Clay. (Box 130, Folder 20)
  - Shuptrine, Phyllis W.. (Box 130, Folder 21)
  - Siler, Colene. (Box 131, Folder 1)
  - Simpson, William S. Jr.. (Box 131, Folder 2)
  - Slagle, Vickie. (Box 131, Folder 3)
  - Slave Values. (Box 131, Folder 4)
  - Smith, Dr. Claiborne. (Box 131, Folder 5)
  - Smith, Clarissa Crenshw. (Box 131, Folder 6)
  - Smith County, TN. (Box 131, Folder 7)
  - Smith County, TN Articles. (Box 131, Folder 8)
  - Smith County, TN Bibles. (Box 131, Folder 9)
  - Smith County, TN Census. (Box 131, Folder 10)
  - Smith County, TN Census (Map-case 56, Drawer 5)
  - Smith County, TN Deeds. (Box 131, Folder 11)
  - Smith County, TN Deeds. (Box 169, Folder 14)
  - Smith County, TN Genealogical Queries. (Box 131, Folder 12)
  - Smith County, TN High School. (Box 131, Folder 13)
  - Smith County, TN History by W.D. Gold. (Box 131, Folder 14)
  - Smith County, TN in World Wars I and II. (Box 131, Folder 15)
  - Smith County, TN Maps. (Box 131, Folder 16)
  - Smith County, TN Powers of Attorney. (Box 131, Folder 17)
  - Smith, Janice Gentry. (Box 131, Folder 18)
  - Smith-Riffe Collection. (Box 131, Folder 19)
  - Social Security Death Index. (Box 131, Folder 20)
  - Social Security Death Index - Smith County, TN. (Box 132, Folder 1-4)
  - South Carolina. (Box 132, Folder 5)
  - South Carolina Research Sources. (Box 132, Folder 6)
  - SW Virginia Materials at UVA Library. (Box 132, Folder 7)
  - Spencer, Katherine. (Box 132, Folder 8)
  - Spradling, Tim. (Box 132, Folder 9)
  - Springfield Plantation (Fayette, MS). (Box 132, Folder 10)
  - Spring Hill Cemetery, Nashville. (Box 132, Folder 11)
  - Stafford County Records. (Box 132, Folder 12)
  - Stanfield-Loving-Brazier Family Bible (Copy and Transcription in "Smith County Bibles" Folder). (Box 164)
  - Stevens, Edwin. (Box 132, Folder 13)
  - Stinson, Mildred. (Box 132, Folder 14)
  - Stock Marks. (Box 132, Folder 15)
  - Stokes, Mai Nell. (Box 132, Folder 16)
  - Stutesman, John Hale. (Box 132, Folder 17)
  - Sumner County, TN. (Box 132, Folder 18)
  - Sumner County, TN Burial Records/Eskew - Illinois. (Box 132, Folder 19)
  - Sumner County, TN Marriages. (Box 132, Folder 20)
  - Swaney, Sue. (Box 132, Folder 21)
  - Swem Library. (Box 133, Folder 1)
  - Sydnor, Richard B. Jr.. (Box 133, Folder 2)
  - Tatum, Rev. Gene C.. (Box 133, Folder 3)
  - Tax Records Missing. (Box 133, Folder 4)
  - Taylor, Dick (Finley). (Box 133, Folder 5)
  - Taylor, Kathryn. (Box 133, Folder 6)
  - Tennessee. (Box 133, Folder 7-8)
  - Tennessee Newspapers. (Box 133, Folder 9)
  - Thiele, Marie Young. (Box 133, Folder 10)
  - Thomas, Edith Allen. (Box 133, Folder 11)
  - Thomas, Edith - Winston-Salem, NC. (Box 133, Folder 12)
  - Tillar, Mrs. B.F.. (Box 133, Folder 13)
  - Tinsley, Sarah Beasley. (Box 133, Folder 14)
  - Tocus, Nora (Starr). (Box 133, Folder 15)
  - Trice, Tim. (Box 133, Folder 16)
  - Trousdale County Historical Society. (Box 133, Folder 17)
  - Universal Calendar. (Box 133, Folder 18)
  - Upper Cumberland Genealogical Association. (Box 133, Folder 19)
  - Villere, Sidney. (Box 133, Folder 20)
  - Virginia County Records. (Box 134, Folder 1-4)
  - "Virginia Genealogical Resources" by Robert Young Clay (Detroit Society for Genealogical Research), 1980. (Box 134, Folder 5)
  - Virginia Genealogical Society, 1991-1992. (Box 134, Folder 6)
  - Virginia Genealogical Society, 1992-1993. (Box 135, Folder 1-3)
  - Virginia Genealogical Society, 1998-1999. (Box 135, Folder 4)
  - Virginia Genealogical Society, 2000. (Box 135, Folder 5)
  - Virginia Historical Society. (Box 135, Folder 6)
  - Virginia Rent Rolls, 1704. (Box 135, Folder 7)
  - Vital Statistics (Plecker). (Box 135, Folder 8)
  - Wade, David D.. (Box 135, Folder 9)
  - Walker. (Box 135, Folder 10)
  - Warren, Mary Bondurant. (Box 135, Folder 11)
  - Washington, DC. (Box 135, Folder 12)
  - Watson, Janet Y.. (Box 135, Folder 13)
  - Watts, Dorothy C.. (Box 135, Folder 14)
  - Wedding Invitations. (Box 135, Folder 15)
  - Weddle, Calvin. (Box 135, Folder 16)
  - Wells, Blanche Clay - Will. (Box 135, Folder 17)
  - Wells, Carter Helm (Jimmy) - Funeral Registers. (Box 135, Folder 18-19)
  - West, H.H.. (Box 135, Folder 20)
  - West Virginia State Archives. (Box 135, Folder 21)
  - West Virginia State Library - County Records on Microfilm. (Box 135, Folder 22)
  - Wilcox, Shirley Langdon. (Box 136, Folder 1)
  - Wilder (Governor's Ancestors). (Box 136, Folder 2)
  - Wilds, James T. Jr.. (Box 136, Folder 3)
  - Will of Lewis Jolly - Brunswick County, VA. (Box 136, Folder 4)
  - Williams, Louise T.. (Box 136, Folder 5)
  - Wilmore, Willie Clay. (Box 136, Folder 6)
  - Wilson County, TN. (Box 136, Folder 7)
  - Wilson, John Scott. (Box 136, Folder 8)
  - Wolfe, Mrs. Clifton. (Box 136, Folder 9)
  - Wood. (Box 136, Folder 10)
  - Wood, Hassie Henderson Tucker. (Box 136, Folder 11)
  - Wood, Helen L.. (Box 136, Folder 12)
  - Woodall, Patty. (Box 136, Folder 13)
  - Wooldridge, William C.. (Box 136, Folder 14)
  - Worley. (Box 136, Folder 15)
  - Yearbooks - The Owl (Smith County High School), 1951-1952. (Box 136)
  - Yearbooks - The Owl (Smith County High School), 1953-1954. (Box 137)
  - Yearbooks - Pillar (George Peabody College), 1970. (Box 137)
  - Young, Frances Hickey. (Box 137, Folder 1-2)
  - Young, Frank. (Box 137, Folder 3)
  - Young, Gentry. (Box 137, Folder 4)
  - Young, Gilbert. (Box 137, Folder 5)
  - Young, Jane E.. (Box 137, Folder 6)
  - Young, Josephine. (Box 138, Folder 1)
  - Young, Larry D.. (Box 138, Folder 2)
  - Young, Maurice. (Box 138, Folder 3)
  - Young, Norma. (Box 138, Folder 4-5)
  - Young, Norma - Clippings and Notes. (Box 138, Folder 6)
  - Young, Norma - Estate. (Box 138, Folder 7)
  - Young, Norma - Genealogical Research. (Box 138, Folder 8)
  - Young, Norvel. (Box 138, Folder 9)
  - Young, Ruth. (Box 138, Folder 10-12)
  - Young, Violet. (Box 138, Folder 13)
  - Young, William Martin. (Box 138, Folder 14)
- Series III. Speech Files, 1974-2005., Extent: 10 boxes. (Box 139-148)
  The Speech Files include texts of Clay's talks and presentations made to various historical and genealogical organizations in Virginia and throughout the country on research methods, the Clay family, sources available at the Library of Virginia, and other topics. The files are arranged alphabetically by the title or subject of his presentation, and then there is a group of "working files" arranged chronologically related to specific speaking engagements, which include correspondence, programs and brochures, information on travel and lodging, calendars, clippings, and contact information.
  - Archives For All People. (Box 139, Folder 1)
  - Asking Genealogical Questions. (Box 139, Folder 2)
  - Background for Talk. (Box 139, Folder 3)
  - Bibliography. (Box 139, Folder 4)
  - Burned Records. (Box 139, Folder 5-6)
  - Church Records. (Box 139, Folder 7)
  - Clay Family. (Box 139, Folder 8)
  - Clues to Virginia Research - Overlooked Bits and Pieces. (Box 139, Folder 9)
  - Colonial and State Records. (Box 139, Folder 10)
  - County Records and Burned. (Box 139, Folder 11)
  - Federal Census Records and Vital Statistics. (Box 139, Folder 12)
  - Finding Your North Carolina Ancestor in the Virginia Archives. (Box 139, Folder 13)
  - Genealogical Problems. (Box 139, Folder 14)
  - Genealogical Research. (Box 140, Folder 1)
  - Genealogical Research in Virginia Records. (Box 140, Folder 2)
  - Handouts. (Box 140, Folder 3)
  - Heraldry. (Box 140, Folder 4)
  - Huguenot Counties. (Box 140, Folder 5)
  - Introduction and County Records. (Box 140, Folder 6)
  - Introduction to Genealogical Research in Virginia. (Box 140, Folder 7-8)
  - An Introduction to Virginia's Local Records. (Box 140, Folder 9)
  - Joining. (Box 140, Folder 10)
  - Land Office Records. (Box 140, Folder 11-12)
  - Land Office Records. (Box 141, Folder 1-2)
  - Making Effective Use of County Court Records in Your Research. (Box 141, Folder 3)
  - Marriage Records. (Box 141, Folder 4)
  - Migration. (Box 141, Folder 5)
  - Military Records. (Box 141, Folder 6-7)
  - Northern Neck Land Office. (Box 141, Folder 8)
  - Personal Papers. (Box 141, Folder 9)
  - Rememberances of Past Researchers, Virginia Genealogical Society. (Box 141, Folder 9a)
  - Rules for Research: Genealogical Do's and Dont's. (Box 141, Folder 10)
  - Summer Research Trip to London. (Box 141, Folder 11)
  - Tax Records and Tithable Lists. (Box 141, Folder 12)
  - Things They Never Tell You. (Box 141, Folder 13-16)
  - Tracing Your Virginia Ancestor. (Box 142, Folder 1)
  - Virginia County Records. (Box 142, Folder 2-3)
  - Virginia Genealogical Research (Introduction to Archives). (Box 142, Folder 3a)
  - Virginia Genealogical Society (Speech About). (Box 142, Folder 4)
  - Virginia Lists. (Box 142, Folder 5)
  - West Augusta District. (Box 142, Folder 6)
  - Why Failure? Overcoming the Amateur's "Throw in the Towel" Syndrome. (Box 142, Folder 7)
  - Why Search for Civil War Records?. (Box 142, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous Speech Notes. (Box 142, Folder 9)
  - Talks, 1974. (Box 142, Folder 10)
  - Talks, 1975. (Box 142, Folder 11)